So, I've decided to start this series
where I'll be sharing my Rider Die
products that I keep on repurchasing with
you guys every now and then.  So today we're going to talk about this
Moody's body mist.
Whenever I take a shower, I immediately
spray this body mist all over my body
and I am not even exaggerating the
moment I step my feet outside the washroom.
Everybody is like, is
that you?  I like
or the best thing about this product is
whenever you put it on it doesn't feel like you have put something on it feels as if you smell like this
naturally but at the same time
it's not overpowering so no you can't
replace your perfumes with this miss this says just that
you know so every day send that would make
you feel fresh hydrated and
mostly so in touch with your feminine side
and this tiny little step has literally become like
a major major part of my
daily self care routine.  And currently I am
about to finish my second bottle and I ca
n't wait to repurchase it.  Was it for this
video.  Comment below if you need
links.